Evil is timeless.
The Diabolical is a horror, science fiction, thriller
film directed by Alistair Legrand.
When a single mother and her two young children are tormented by an increasingly strange and intense presence in their quiet suburban
home, she turns to her scientist boyfriend to take on the violent forces that paranormal experts are too frightened to face.
Madison, played by Ali Larter.
Nikolai, played by Arjun Gupta.
Haley, played by Chloe Perrin.
Carl, played by Joe Egender.
Austin, played by Patrick Fischler.
Miguel, played by Wilmer Calderon.
The Diabolical is a 2015 American science fiction horror film directed by
Alistair Legrand and written by Legrand and Luke Harvis.
It stars Ali Larter as a single mother who battles evil forces in her house.
It premiered at SXSW in March 2015 and, after being released
internationally, received a limited release in the US in October 2015.
The film explores themes of parapsychology, absurd, baffled, complicated.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.